That's it, I'm out of here.
(Past Leonard:)Joyce, come on.
Twelve hours?
(Penny:)Oh, my God.
(Leonard:)-Do I get some sympathy now?
-Little bit.
(Penny:)Let me get this straight.
You move in with this guy, makes
you sign a ridiculous roommate agreement.
(Penny:)Then he walks into your bedroom
while you're doing Joyce Kim...
(Penny:)...and you still stay?
(Leonard:)Actually, I couldn't get too mad at him
about Joyce Kim.
(Penny:)Why not?
(Leonard:)Well, I was doing some
government research at the time.
You know, military rocket fuels.
Kind of secret.
-What does that have to do with Joyce?
-As it turns out...
(Leonard:)...she was a North Korean spy.
(Leonard:)Luckily, Sheldon drove her out
before I revealed anything important.
(Leonard:)Which I'm not saying I would have.
So you stayed with Sheldon
all this time...
(Penny:)...because he kept you from going
to federal prison?
That's part of it. The other part is
what happened with the elevator.